

## **Overview**

Matt brings over 15 years of experience in agency work to his role as Director of Design at Phase2. His excellence with clients, his strategic thinking, his proven UI design skills, and his passion for all things brand make him a key contributor on any project.

Prior to joining Phase2, Matt held various creative and frontend development agency roles, most recently as the Creative Director at Unleashed Technologies. He is passionate about design systems, establishing engaging web experiences, and bringing clients' brands to life in the digital space.

# **Experience**

**Galley Creative Group** 

**Phase2 Technology** 2021 - Present **Design Director Unleashed Technologies** 2011 - 2021 Creative Director Sr. Frontend Developer Web Designer

# **Skills**

Web Designer

- Figma
- Design systems
- HTML 5 / CSS3

- Ul design
- Prototyping
- Github

2009 - 2011

- UX design
- Adobe CC
- Product design

#### **Contact**

**Portfolio** 

mattjcurtin.com

**Email** 

mjcurtin1@gmail.com

## **Education**

University of Maryland, **Baltimore County (UMBC)** BA, Graphic Design, Media Communications 2009

## **Awards**

**AM&P Excel Award: Air Force** Magazine

2021

**Davey Association Award:** 

**AMIA** 

2021

**Communicator Award:** 

**Extraco Banks** 

2021

W3 Award — Best General

Website: NAFSA

2019

Davey Award — Best

**Association Website: NGAUS** 

2019